[{
    "Question": "align-content",
    "Answer": "Specifies the alignment between the lines inside a flexible container when the items do not use all available space"
  },
  {
    "Question": "align-items",
    "Answer": "Specifies the alignment for items inside a flexible container"
  },
  {
    "Question": "align-self",
    "Answer": "Specifies the alignment for selected items inside a flexible container"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex",
    "Answer": "Specifies the length of the item, relative to the rest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex-basis",
    "Answer": "Specifies the initial length of a flexible item"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex-direction",
    "Answer": "Specifies the direction of the flexible items"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex-flow",
    "Answer": "A shorthand property for the flex-direction and the flex-wrap properties"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex-grow",
    "Answer": "Specifies how much the item will grow relative to the rest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex-shrink",
    "Answer": "Specifies how the item will shrink relative to the rest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flex-wrap",
    "Answer": "Specifies whether the flexible items should wrap or not"
  },
  {
    "Question": "justify-content",
    "Answer": "Specifies the alignment between the items inside a flexible container when the items do not use all available space"
  },
  {
    "Question": "order",
    "Answer": "Sets the order of the flexible item, relative to the rest"
  }
]
